Preliminary Guide to the Lisner Auditorium records, 1946-2005 RG0055
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Posters, 1967-1988; RG0055 Series 1; 8 Linear feet (Box 6, Box 7, Box 5, Box 3, Box 4, Box 2, Box 1, Box 8, Box 9)
  - Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, 04/16/1988 (Box 4, Folder 309)
  - Kiss Me Kate, 11/13/1975-11/15/1975 (Box 4, Folder 310)
  - Kiss Me Kate, 11/13/1975-11/15/1975 (Box 4, Folder 311)
  - D'Oly Carte Opera Company, Gilbert and Sullivan - October 18-20, undated (Box 4, Folder 312)
  - D'Oly Carte Opera Company, Gilbert and Sullivan - October 18-20, undated (Box 4, Folder 313)
  - The Kingston Trio - June 10, undated (Box 4, Folder 314)
  - Bill Monroe, Don Reno, Bill Harrell, 03/09/1973 (Box 4, Folder 315)
  - Bill Monroe, Don Reno, Bill Harrell, 03/09/1973 (Box 4, Folder 316)
  - Jerry Jeff Walker and the Flying Burrito Brothers - October 26-28, undated (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - The Spiritual Viewpoint - September 27, undated (Box 4, Folder 318)
  - Richard Smallwood Singers - September 30, undated (Box 4, Folder 319)
  - A.F.I. Film Festival at Kennedy Center - October 14-23, undated (Box 4, Folder 320)
  - David Bromberg Band, 04/22/1980 (Box 5, Folder 321)
  - Make New Banners, undated (Box 5, Folder 322)
  - Los 4 de Cordoba, 05/31/1984 (Box 5, Folder 323)
  - Poster in Korean, undated (Box 5, Folder 324)
  - Franco Luambo Makiadi and the T.P.O.K Jazz Band - November 11-12, undated (Box 5, Folder 325)
  - Franco Luambo Makiadi and the T.P.O.K Jazz Band - November 11-12, undated (Box 5, Folder 326)
  - El Greco of Toledo, 06/12/1982 (Box 5, Folder 327)
  - Tom Paxton, 04/20/1968 (Box 5, Folder 328)
  - Holly Near, 03/26/1988 (Box 5, Folder 329)
  - Here's Brother Brigham - January 5-6, undated (Box 5, Folder 330)
  - Han Wei Goodwill Mission. R.O.C., 10/10/1987 (Box 5, Folder 331)
  - Triumphant Return of the Chieftains - March 10, undated (Box 5, Folder 332)
  - Ram Dass, 04/23/1982 (Box 5, Folder 333)
  - Maryland Dance Theatre - January 23, undated (Box 5, Folder 334)
  - Washington Ballet - February 12-21, undated (Box 5, Folder 335)
  - Calyspso Extravaganza with Mighty Sparrow, 06/06/1981 (Box 5, Folder 336)
  - Calypso Revue, 04/30/1988 (Box 5, Folder 337)
  - Le Pavillon au Bord de la Riviere, undated (Box 5, Folder 338)
  - United States Marine Corp Band Concert Series, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 339)
  - The Hudson River Sloop Restoration (Pete Seeger, Jimmy Collin, Gordon Bok autograph), undated (Box 5, Folder 340)
  - Usha Uthup (Iyer) - August 20, undated (Box 5, Folder 341)
  - Comedy '87, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 342)
  - Paul Winter Consort - September 28, undated (Box 5, Folder 343)
  - Cambodian Dance and Music, 12/12/1981 (Box 5, Folder 344)
  - Paco Pena (autographed) - October 11, undated (Box 5, Folder 345)
  - Bobby and the Midnites - November 8, undated (Box 5, Folder 346)
  - The Three Cuckolds, 03/15/1968-03/16/1968 (Box 5, Folder 347)
  - Kalesang Galing Maynila - September 23, undated (Box 5, Folder 348)
  - Montoya, Flamenco guitarist, 03/20/1971 (Box 5, Folder 349)
  - "Oneness of Ju Ju" - April 27, undated (Box 5, Folder 350)
  - Ballet Folkorico de Chile - October 12, undated (Box 5, Folder 351)
  - Trisha Brown Dance Company - November 3-4, undated (Box 5, Folder 352)
  - Wolfe Tones - March 10, undated (Box 5, Folder 353)
  - Gil-Scott Heron and Zupata - March 22, undated (Box 5, Folder 354)
  - America Awakes - May 29, undated (Box 5, Folder 355)
  - Youth Goodwill Mission, 11/02/1986 (Box 5, Folder 356)
  - John Fahey with Insect Trust - May 2, undated (Box 5, Folder 357)
  - Bluegrass Winter Festival with Seldom Scene, John Sterling, the Johnson Mountain Boys, undated (Box 5, Folder 358)
  - Ebenezer Obey - August 14, undated (Box 5, Folder 359)
  - Ebenezer Obey - August 14, undated (Box 5, Folder 360)
  - 30th Anniversary of Japan Admitted to the U.N. (with booklet), 04/12/1987 (Box 5, Folder 361)
  - The Chiffons, 05/05/1967 (Box 5, Folder 362)
  - Marcel Khalife, 04/30/1982 (Box 5, Folder 363)
  - Mighty Wurlitzer, undated (Box 5, Folder 364)
  - Eurythmeum Stuttgart - October 15, undated (Box 5, Folder 365)
  - Margie Adam, 06/14/1980 (Box 5, Folder 366)
  - Inward to the Sea, 09/08/1973 (Box 5, Folder 367)
  - Inward to the Sea, 09/08/1973 (Box 5, Folder 368)
  - Roy Buchanan with Nighthawks, 12/02/1973 (Box 5, Folder 369)
  - Arthur C. Clarke, 04/30/1981 (Box 5, Folder 370)
  - Caribbean Extravaganza, 06/01/1985 (Box 5, Folder 371)
  - Israeli Folk Dance Festival, 4th annual - April 4, undated (Box 5, Folder 372)
  - The Salvation Army Centennial Concert, 05/17/1985-05/19/1985 (Box 5, Folder 373)
  - International Night, 03/22/1968 (Box 5, Folder 374)
  - Le Misanthrope - March 1, undated (Box 5, Folder 375)
  - Black Voices - May 9, undated (Box 5, Folder 376)
  - Paul Taylor Dance company - April 6-7, undated (Box 5, Folder 377)
  - Ghulam Ali, 10/03/1986 (Box 5, Folder 378)
  - Ukranian Chorus Zhurarli, 10/09/1986 (Box 5, Folder 379)
  - Washington Ballet - The Nutcracker - December 11-January 4, undated (Box 5, Folder 380)
  - Lana Turner - November 18, undated (Box 5, Folder 381)
  - Irish Spring Benefit - April 27, undated (Box 5, Folder 382)
  - From Vienna with Love, undated (Box 5, Folder 383)
  - Pankaj Udhas in Concert, 04/10/1987 (Box 5, Folder 384)
  - Le Nozze di Figaro, 03/29/1974-03/31/1974 (Box 5, Folder 385)
  - New York Rainbow Terrace Calypso Tent, 08/13/1983 (Box 5, Folder 386)
  - Peking Acrobats, undated (Box 5, Folder 387)
  - GW Dance Company, 04/25/1969-04/26/1969 (Box 5, Folder 388)
  - Grover Washington Jr. - November 13, undated (Box 5, Folder 389)
  - Grover Washington Jr. - November 13, undated (Box 5, Folder 390)
  - Kun Woo Paik Piano concert, 09/22/1984 (Box 5, Folder 391)
  - Ballet Folklorico De Chile - October 12, undated (Box 5, Folder 392)
  - The Photographer (exhibit), 03/09/1984 (Box 5, Folder 393)
  - The Photographer (exhibit), 03/09/1984 (Box 5, Folder 394)
  - Ethel Butler Company - October 28, undated (Box 5, Folder 395)
  - Koanga - December 18-21, undated (Box 5, Folder 396)
  - Washington Ballet - April 18-19, undated (Box 5, Folder 397)
  - Reda Eqyptian Dance Troupe, 07/20/1984 (Box 5, Folder 398)
  - Laser Dance, 05/06/1985-05/07/1985 (Box 5, Folder 399)
  - Pery Ribeiro - October 18, undated (Box 5, Folder 400)
  - Eric Hawkins - April 29-30, undated (Box 6, Folder 401)
  - Jay Leno, 09/21/1983 (Box 6, Folder 402)
  - Over 40 Mr. DC, 06/04/1983 (Box 6, Folder 403)
  - Washington Ballet - Nutcracker, 12/07/1978-12/30/1978 (Box 6, Folder 404)
  - Trinidad Tripoli Steel Band, 11/21/1971 (Box 6, Folder 405)
  - "Children of a Lesser God" movie poster, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 406)
  - National Ballet1968-, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 407)
  - Le Bourgeoi Gentilhomme, 11/29/1971 (Box 6, Folder 408)
  - Le Bourgeoi Gentilhomme, 11/29/1971 (Box 6, Folder 409)
  - Ida Kaminska, 06/18/1979 (Box 6, Folder 410)
  - Preservation Hall Jazz Band, 05/10/1969 (Box 6, Folder 411)
  - New York Pro Musica, 02/03/1968 (Box 6, Folder 412)
  - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes, 01/26/1967-02/19/1967 (Box 6, Folder 413)
  - Inward to the Sea, 11/09/1985 (Box 6, Folder 414)
  - Inward to the Sea, 09/25/1976 (Box 6, Folder 415)
  - Washington Ballet season, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 416)
  - Korean Concert, 06/28/1975 (Box 6, Folder 417)
  - Don Redlich Dance company - October 29-30, undated (Box 6, Folder 418)
  - Mari Elizabeth Morgen, 07/14/1976 (Box 6, Folder 419)
  - Dream Girls (posters and booklet), 10/1982 (Box 6, Folder 420)
  - Two Widows, 10/26/1974 (Box 6, Folder 421)
  - Christmas Revels, 12/02/1983-12/03/1983 (Box 6, Folder 422)
  - Tommy Makem & liam Clancy farewell tour (autographed by Clancy), 03/1988 (Box 6, Folder 423)
  - Bach Birthday Bash with Mark Russell, 03/21/1988 (Box 6, Folder 424)
  - Economics As if People Matter, 03/21/1977 (Box 6, Folder 425)
  - Frank Sherr piano concert - November 1, undated (Box 6, Folder 426)
  - Physique Competition, 06/14/1986 (Box 6, Folder 427)
  - Fishbone, Berlin, Suzanne Vega, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 428)
  - Tim Weisberg, 03/15/1974 (Box 6, Folder 429)
  - Washington National Symphony coupon book, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 430)
  - Jagjit and Chitra Singh - May 10, undated (Box 6, Folder 431)
  - Wolfe Tones, 03/02/1984 (Box 6, Folder 432)
  - Willie Clancy Summer School - April 10, undated (Box 6, Folder 433)
  - Capilla Alfonsina, undated (Box 6, Folder 434)
  - Alfonso Reyes, 11/26/1981 (Box 6, Folder 435)
  - Edward Tarr & George Kent - October 26, undated (Box 6, Folder 436)
  - Grand Canyon by Dory, 04/07/1983 (Box 6, Folder 437)
  - "Islands in the Stream" movie poster, 04/28/1977 (Box 6, Folder 438)
  - Firesign Theatre "Proctor & Bergman" - March 8, undated (Box 6, Folder 439)
  - Tim Weisberg, 03/15/1974 (Box 6, Folder 440)
  - International Staff Songsters of the Salvation Army, 12/11/1986 (Box 6, Folder 441)
  - Grupo Cultural Venezuela - October 31, undated (Box 6, Folder 442)
  - Dance Essence - June 15, undated (Box 6, Folder 443)
  - Doc and Merle Watson - October 31, undated (Box 6, Folder 444)
  - Inti-illimani, 09/18/1985 (Box 6, Folder 445)
  - Carolyn Forche and Pete Seeger, 07/19/1984 (Box 6, Folder 446)
  - Bluegrass Winter Festival, 02/05/1984 (Box 6, Folder 447)
  - Joyce Bryant, 04/30/1978 (Box 6, Folder 448)
  - U.S. Navy Band Jazz ensemble, 03/29/1981 (Box 6, Folder 449)
  - Dylan Thomas Growing Up - October 21, undated (Box 6, Folder 450)
  - George Faison - December 5-6, undated (Box 6, Folder 451)
  - Ewha Womans University Dance Performance, 03/12/1975 (Box 6, Folder 452)
  - Wolfe Tones, undated (Box 6, Folder 453)
  - Hai Chia Variety Show, undated (Box 6, Folder 454)
  - Los Jaivas - April 19, undated (Box 6, Folder 455)
  - Princeton Triangle Club - December 22, undated (Box 6, Folder 456)
  - Peter Pears and Julian Bream - February 24, undated (Box 6, Folder 457)
  - Norbert Brainin (violinist) - June 6, undated (Box 6, Folder 458)
  - A Taste of Ireland, undated (Box 6, Folder 459)
  - Spring in Spain, 03/23/1984 (Box 6, Folder 460)
  - J.S. Bach International Competition, 06/11/1971-06/13/1971 (Box 6, Folder 461)
  - Stearns Miners Benefit with Pete Seeger, 06/08/1979 (Box 6, Folder 462)
  - Ballet National Djoliba - February 24-28, undated (Box 6, Folder 463)
  - Le Ballet National Djoliba - February 24-28, undated (Box 6, Folder 464)
  - Jean-Pierre Jumez - March 19, undated (Box 6, Folder 465)
  - Film Fest D.C. (Autographed by Maya Plitsetskaya), 04/20/1988-05/01/1988 (Box 6, Folder 466)
  - Inner City Repertory Dance Company, 10/27/1973 (Box 6, Folder 467)
  - Schooner Fare - May 4, undated (Box 6, Folder 468)
  - Ballet Folklorico de Chile Pucara - September 18, undated (Box 6, Folder 469)
  - Dance Theatre of Harlem at Kennedy Center, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 470)
  - Itzhak Perlman - April 10, undated (Box 6, Folder 471)
  - Christian Science lecture - April 12, undated (Box 6, Folder 472)
  - Fantasy with Lady & Crossbow, 01/15/1977 (Box 6, Folder 473)
  - Ballet Folklorico de Chile Pucara - September 18, undated (Box 6, Folder 474)
  - Canterbury Tales, 11/16/1972-11/19/1972 (Box 6, Folder 475)
  - Rusalka (Antonic Dvorack), 09/15/1972-09/16/1972 (Box 6, Folder 476)
  - Rusalka (Antonic Dvorack), 09/15/1972-09/16/1972 (Box 6, Folder 477)
  - Replacements - November 18, undated (Box 6, Folder 478)
  - Washington Area Music Awards (1st annual) - September 29, undated (Box 6, Folder 479)
  - The Benoit / Freeman Project - May 1, undated (Box 6, Folder 480)
  - Mecca Melodiers (Shriners), 04/29/1979 (Box 7, Folder 481)
  - Maryland Ballet- November 3, undated (Box 7, Folder 482)
  - Twyla Tharp, 10/04/1977 (Box 7, Folder 483)
  - Horacio Guarany- May 28, undated (Box 7, Folder 484)
  - J.S. Bach International Competition - August 22-24, undated (Box 7, Folder 485)
  - Montgomery County Youth Orchestra, 04/25/1971 (Box 7, Folder 486)
  - Requesh Israeli Folklore Ensemble - January 28, undated (Box 7, Folder 487)
  - Radiodrengekort (Danish Club of Washington Radio Boys' Choir), 10/15/1972 (Box 7, Folder 488)
  - Beate Klarsfeld (Nazi hunter) - November 1, undated (Box 7, Folder 489)
  - Voces de America Canciones Eterna del Ayer - May 30, undated (Box 7, Folder 490)
  - D.C. Youth Orchestra - February 22, undated (Box 7, Folder 491)
  - Hai Chia Variety Show, R.O.C., undated (Box 7, Folder 492)
  - T.V. Stars of Pakistan "No Problem" - October 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 493)
  - Julian Bream, 10/12/1988 (Box 7, Folder 494)
  - Tommy Makem & Liam Clancy "Two for the Dew" - March 12, undated (Box 7, Folder 495)
  - Beat of Ukraine, Kuban Cossacks, undated (Box 7, Folder 496)
  - Romanovsky & Phillips - September 13, undated (Box 7, Folder 497)
  - National Debate on Pornography - November 1, undated (Box 7, Folder 498)
  - La Nozze di Figaro, 03/29/1974-03/31/1974 (Box 7, Folder 499)
  - George Benson, 10/31/1974 (Box 7, Folder 500)
  - Universidad de Chile Ballet Folklorico, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 501)
  - Claude Kipnis, 04/22/1977-04/23/1977 (Box 7, Folder 502)
  - Joe Cocker, 04/30/1970 (Box 7, Folder 503)
  - GWU Dance Company, 03/02/1969 (Box 7, Folder 504)
  - National Folklore theatre of Ireland - September 26, undated (Box 7, Folder 505)
  - Washington Ballet - February 1-2, undated (Box 7, Folder 506)
  - Triumphant Return of the Chieftains - October 12, undated (Box 7, Folder 507)
  - Brook Benton and the Mighty Sparrow, 08/23/1986 (Box 7, Folder 508)
  - Clancy Brothers - March 19, undated (Box 7, Folder 509)
  - Clancy Brothers and Tommy Makem - February 18, undated (Box 7, Folder 510)
  - Festival of the Nations - May 17, 20, 23, 26, June 1, undated (Box 7, Folder 511)
  - Inward to the Sea, 09/20/1974-09/21/1974 (Box 7, Folder 512)
  - Inward to the Sea, 11/14/1987 (Box 7, Folder 513)
  - Doc Watson and Son, 01/28/1973 (Box 7, Folder 514)
  - Joffrey II Dancers, 05/18/1981 (Box 7, Folder 515)
  - Joffrey II Dancers, 05/18/1981 (Box 7, Folder 516)
  - Twyla Tharp Dance Foundation - April 24-26, undated (Box 7, Folder 517)
  - The Eternal Flame - October 16, undated (Box 7, Folder 518)
  - Doodling (a play), 10/15/1982-10/16/1982 (Box 7, Folder 519)
  - Jesus Christ Superstar - October 16-21, undated (Box 7, Folder 520)
  - Jesus Christ Superstar - October 16-21, undated (Box 7, Folder 521)
  - La Forza del Destino - November 28-29, undated (Box 7, Folder 522)
  - Elmar Oliveira (at Kennedy Center), 01/30/1982 (Box 7, Folder 523)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, 03/04/1977-03/05/1977 (Box 7, Folder 524)
  - Nikolais Dance Theatre, 11/08/1974-11/09/1974 (Box 7, Folder 525)
  - Mummenschanz, 11/16/1974 (Box 7, Folder 526)
  - Mummenschanz, 11/16/1974 (Box 7, Folder 527)
  - Fotem Turkish Dance ensemble - April 10-11, undated (Box 7, Folder 528)
  - Ballet Spectacular - October 24, undated (Box 7, Folder 529)
  - Aida, 05/08/1980-05/10/1980 (Box 7, Folder 530)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company - January 23-24, undated (Box 7, Folder 531)
  - National Ballet - February 21-23, undated (Box 7, Folder 532)
  - National Ballet - February 21-23, undated (Box 7, Folder 533)
  - Fu Hsing Chinese Opera, 03/17/1985 (Box 7, Folder 534)
  - GWU Dance Company - April 22-23, undated (Box 7, Folder 535)
  - Kuang Hua Goodwill Mission R.O.C., 10/12/1985 (Box 7, Folder 536)
  - "Coppelia" Regional Ballet Company of Washington - February 11, undated (Box 7, Folder 537)
  - Erick Hawkins and Dance Company - October 11, undated (Box 7, Folder 538)
  - Virgil Fox, 12/06/1985 (Box 7, Folder 539)
  - Hoofers are Here - October 7-9, undated (Box 7, Folder 540)
    General note
    Framed
  - National Dance Theater of Zaire, 11/11/1981 (Box 7, Folder 541)
  - Erick Hawkins and Dance Company - October 11, undated (Box 7, Folder 542)
  - Laser Dance, 05/06/1985-05/07/1985 (Box 7, Folder 543)
  - Spring Fling Party in the Quad, 04/25/1982 (Box 7, Folder 546)
  - Doodling (a play), 08/29/1981 (Box 7, Folder 547)
  - Nikolais Dance Theatre, 11/08/1974-11/09/1974 (Box 8, Folder 544)
  - Washington Ballet, Spring Series, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 545)
- Office files, 1961-1985; RG0055 Series 2; 13.5 Linear feet (Box 3)
  This series contains contracts, office files, fiscal reports, schedules, activities calendars, programs, etc. The original numbering scheme of the folders inside the boxes has been maintained. They materials range in date from 1961-1985.
  Formerly ACC#37; original folder numbering has been maintained, which is contiuous from the first to last box.
  - American Light Opera Company (ALOC), 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Arts Association, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Bach Foundation, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American University Student Association, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Armenian Students' Association of America Inc, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Atlantic Skin Diving Council, 1972-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Augsburg College Choir, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ballet Washington, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ballou Senior High School, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Argentine Embassy - Martha Argerich, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Brazilian Embassy - Guiomar Novaes, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Folklore Society of Greater Washington - Clancy Broth, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Girl Scouts of US Region 3 Nat. Conference, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - GWU Medical Center Closing Assembly, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Inter-American Development Bank-17th Anniversary, 1967-1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Johann Sebastian Bach Intern. Competitions, 1967-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Lower Lisner, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Muscular Dystrophy Assoc. of America Inc., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Peabody Institute of Baltimore - Peabody Symph. Orch, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Princeton Club of Washington Musical Comedy, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Private Arts Foundation - Merce Cunningham, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Rutgers University Wind Ensemble - Cancelled, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - St. Colubans Foreign Mission Society Benefit Concert, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Southwest Community Council Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Vietnam, Embassy Cultural Variety Show, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Washington Childrens Fund Inc., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Wash. Music Teachers' Assoc. Inc. - Children's Progr., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - National Ballet Society Inc. - Ballet Perf., 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Washington National Symphony - Harkness Ballet, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Washington National Symphony - Symphonic Programs, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - New Educational Ways Inc. - Charlie Byrd, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Oratorio Society of Montgomery County, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Washington Performing Arts Society, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Washington Performing Arts Society, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Patrick Hayes, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Washington Performing Arts Society, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Washington Performing Arts Society, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Washington Performing - Arts Society, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Baylor University Choir, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Belli Seminar Foundation, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Bicentennial Commission of; the District of Columbia, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Brazilian Embassy, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - British Tourist Authority, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Capitol Ballet Guild - Jones Haywood, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Cardinal Mindszenty Society by Kossuth Foundation, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Catholic University of America School of Music, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Centre Benefico Panamericano, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - D.C. Coordinating Committee Intern. Women's Year, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - D.C. Recreation, 1971-1981 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - The Danish Club of Washington, D.C., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Dong Go Foundation CooperatingBoard Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Drivers, Chauffeurs and Helpers Local Union 639, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - llth Christian Workshop - Christian Meth. Esp. Churcl, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Ewha Womans University, Inc. (Intern. Foundation), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - William H. Farble Production Community, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Federal Aviation Administration ARD-700, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Forest View High School, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Friends of the National Zoo, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Georgiana Thomas Grand Chapter - Order of Eastern Star, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - German Language Society - The Castile, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Great lakes Association for the Dance Inc., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Guinea, Embassy of the Republic of, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Guyana, Embassy of (Caribbean American Interc. Org.), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - HELP (Lester Grossman), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Humanity, Church of, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Hungarian Freedom Fighters Federation Inc., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Interamerican Choral Society, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - International Fiscal Association, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - International Repertory Co. & Ballet, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Israel, Embassy of, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Jewish Foundation for Retarded Children, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Faifax Jubil-Aires, Inc., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - The Korean Student Fund, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Living Theatre, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Mali, Embassy - Mali Ballet, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Maryland Youth Ballet, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Memorial Evangelical Lutheran Church (Luther Place), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Wash. Area Conv. & Vis. Bur. of the Metro Wash BrdTrade, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Montgomery County Youth Orchestra Ass., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Musicians, Federation of Local 161-710, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - National Ballet of Washington, 1963-1973 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Opera Society of Washington, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Opera Society of Washington, 1969-1976 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Pastoral Counseling and Consultation Centers, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Peabody Institute, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - People's Congregational Church, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Pioneer Women, (Greater Washington Council of), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Polish National Alliance Counciil 203, 1969-1974 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Princeton Club of D.C., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - The Quaterly Review (American Council of Polish Cult), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Nonmedical Drug Use, The Center for the study of, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - North Washington Neighbours, Inc (Bob Bialek,Disc.Rec), 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Opera America Inc., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Quest, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Roadwork (AUX), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Saint Anthony Catholic Church, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - St. Gabiel's Church (Timothy Chenley's Variety Show), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Sino-American Cultural Society, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Sivananda Yoga Vedanta Centre, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Society for New Presentations (SNAP) -contracts only, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Solomon Schechter School of Greater Washington, Inc, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - School of Nursing Wash. Hosp. Ctr Student Coop. Assoc, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Temple Micah, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Unification Church (The Holy Spirit Ass. for Unif W.Ch, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - United Holy Land Fund, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - The U.S. Marine Band, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Republic of Vietnam (Embassy of the), 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Washington Ballet Company, 1974-1986 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Washington Ballet Company (AUX), 1974-1985 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Washington International College, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 112)